[INTRO] Because it can give you stronger Angulation.
[INTRO] With the feeling that the pelvis sticks as fast as possible.
[INTRO] Because of these two problems
[INTRO] Turn this part around, look at it 10 times, look at it 100 times.
[INTRO] I hope you don't really go through this problem.
[INTRO] Thank you.
Hello, I'm self-study boarder Kim Seungwon.
You practiced Angulation last time.
At this time,
Let's practice angulation while down.
It's an apocryphal state of down, but I'm not going to mix down and up.
It's an Angulation state, but I'm not going to mix Down and Up.
You'll practice giving an Angulation while keeping it down.
Now, let me show you how you can do the Angulation while down.
In the case of toe-turn, you practiced angulation last time
with your pelvis open and your hands up the upper front leg.
The low angulation posture is not much different from this.
As we practiced the low BBP position before,
if this high BBP position is like this,
it feels like you're sitting in the axial direction.
The pelvis goes down to the rear boot
and the face goes down to the front boot,
so you can lower it like this.
In my case, when I do toe-turn, I wear both boots together. ...
It's not even, but it's kind of like pressing down on the front boot.
Please note that this may vary depending on the style of the riders.
In my case, I usually ride, I don't stretch out my front leg when I go down,
but I lean my front boot together like this,
press the front boot through my upper body, and give it a press,
so I don't bend my upper body too much,
but I usually ride with my upper body slightly up.
I hope you can refer to this part
Now, let me show you heel side turn
Now, let me show you the heel-turn.
you would have give the angulation from the high BBP position.
In case of the heel-turn, it doesn't feel like you're sitting on both legs like toe-turn
It's like you're sitting over the tail side.
In other words, rather than rear boot, it's more like sitting on a tail, so that your pelvis doesn't lean forward during the turn.
I think it could be an important tip that won't loosen up your pelvis.
Now, when the heel-turn goes over, don't sit in front of it,
but as if you're sitting towards the tail,
fold your pelvis like this.
At this time, the hand goes up over the front boot,
you can fold the pelvis like this
Let me tell you some precautions when using Angulation while down.
If you do Angulation while down, you will be very close to the body.
You're supposed to want to touch the ground without even realizing it.
Don't touch your hands at this time.
And with the intention of keeping your hands away from the slope,
Angulation, as practiced before,
In case of toe-turn, raise your right arm a little higher,
In the case of a heel-turn, it would be nice if you could raise your left arm like this
instead of trying to touch the slope with your hands.
This time, I'm going to show you carving using Angulation in a low BBP position.
As I showed you in the high position,
angulation in the low position is only low,
but the way you ride is the same.
The shoulder line should be parallel to the slope.
Especially in the lower position, the angulation can be stronger,
so you have to push the pelvis as hard as possible with the feeling that the pelvis sticks to the slope first.
When tilting,
you have to do a toe-turn with the pelvis is toe-turn.
If you lower your posture when you do a heel-turn,
your pelvis will probably fall out easily.
Please keep your pelvis rotated BBP position so that your pelvis won't loosen up
and try using heel side angulation and down.
The pelvis does not fall
Please try carving using the hillside outer diameter and down
Now let me show you.
Now in the down position ~
At this time, do not hold your hand to clean it,
Even if you are made backward shifted weight a little,
be careful not to tilt your upper body towards the nose.
Otherwise, the edge grip will loosen.
Also, when you do edge change, please practice while controlling up as much as possible.
Of course, I'm going to mix up and down later.
If you practice now,
you're practicing to balance your pelvic rotation in a down position,
but if you mix up and down, your pelvis will be released while you're up and down.
The balance can be broken
So please keep your position as low as possible and practice.
Thank you
I've explained to you about the problem
that we're expecting.
I thought you guys would have a lot of problems and hardships during this practice,
so I thought it would be better to explain it in more detail,
so I decided to dub it like this.
So, each section is divided into three stages: turn start, turn progress, and turn finish.
and I'm going to give you an additional explanation.
First, toe-turn.
This is toe-turn start.
You're supposed to be in a neutral position, a low BBP position,
when you're entering the toe-turn.
I'm not perfect looking at my posture right now.
The pelvis is jutted out.
If you're going to try to get into the toe-turn in this low position,
you're more likely to have a bad neutral position.
Even if you don't like your posture,
it's important that you try to have an open neutral position.
It is very important to try to have
From this point on, if the upper body is closed,
It's too difficult to get in with your hips jutted out.
So it's important to make sure that your pelvis doesn't come out
and your upper body is open and the turn enters.
And as you can see, when you tilt at the stage of entering the turn,
I'm not dropping my head,
I'm just getting on it like I'm pushing my pelvis towards the slope.
If you look at the process of going up from the heel-turn and entering the toe-turn,
you can see that the pelvis is used to tilt.
You push it like this, you enter the turn,
and you keep lifting your right shoulder.
Now, you can see the pelvis pushed in like this.
You may think that you actually put your pelvis in,
but you actually have to put it in really hard,
so you can feel it going in like this.
If you can film a video when you're on the ride,
make sure to check your position, whether your hips is jutted out much,
or if your head is bent like this.
I think you should check it.
And the end of the turn is to reduce the rebound as much as possible,
and then pull it up slowly.
At this time, since we didn't use up, don't do up as much as you can,
and feel like you're just getting up.
What I want to warn you is that
if you're a person who was good at carving
and you're a person who's good at speeding up
If you're watching this video because you're not good enough right now,
maybe you can use rebound to quickly pass the turn.
But if you think I'm not good at Angulation,
and if you think there's something unstable in a down position,
never change edges using rebounding
When you practice, you try to ride without your advanced skills as much as possible
I focus only on the part I lack
It is very important to practice
Actually, it's much easier for me to do edge change using rebound.
Now that I'm used to it, it's much more comfortable,
but if I ride it like that again, I'm afraid you'll follow me and get in a bad posture.
So, I don't use advanced technology as much as,
I'm riding like this even if it's uncomfortable
So even if you know how to do the rebound, please refrain from doing that as much as you can and focus on the necessary practice.
At this time it's a heel-turn.
It's starting heel-turn.
Heel-turn's turn-starting gives you the exact low BBP position you've seen before.
Especially in the heel-turn, the position of turn starting is very important.
It's very likely that your pelvic rotation isn't very good
when you see them entering the heel-turn while practicing.
But if we do side-sleeping or do a lot of practice,
we can do it if you practice a little bit while you can do it.
Please enter with pelvic rotation as this is possible.
This is turn progress.
Now, if you just look at the turn,
you'll see that your pelvis is slightly loosened.
When I make a turn, my pelvis is slightly loosened,
and in order to maintain it, as I've explained before,
you have to ride it with the feeling that you continue to lead the gaze, the body, and the pelvis.
Now~ Like this~ You can see that it's leading the upper body, right?
There's really little rotation,
but you have to feel like you're doing a rotation.
At this time, you need to be careful about your front leg.
You can see the pelvis is slightly leaned towards the front leg
In fact, it's a little leaned even though it's holding out through "stretching its front leg."
If you look at the video of your actual ride,
your pelvis could be in front of your front leg
or just on your front leg.
Not if that happens.
If you hold your front leg as long as you can, you need to feel them.
Look at the toe-turn again.
You can push your pelvis in.
You can enter the heel-turn and ride it like this
as if you are in the BBP position and lead the upper body.
The common problem with toe-turns is,
like I said before, that your pelvis will jut out,
and you can ride them like you're pushing your pelvis, so that's relatively easy.
Mostly, ride toe-turn more comfortably.
There are two common problems with the heel-turn,
the first thing is that as soon as you enter the turn, your pelvis just pulls to the front leg.
The tail edge grip is broken as soon as you start heel-turn.
The reason is that the front leg of BBP
with low turn-start position should be stretched to prevent the pelvis from leaning forward,
and the pelvis should be placed over the rear leg as much as possible,
As much as possible, you should enter with the feeling of sitting in the tail.
but if you try to enter the heel-turn comfortably,
the pelvis will be pulled to the front and you will be forced to sit on the front leg.
If you're leaning on your front leg, you'll never be able to pull it out with your rear leg again.
So if you focus and practice when you make the turn,
you can solve the problem.
Second, I made a good turn-start.
As you progress, your rear leg stretch out
Maybe your rear leg are stretched out,
but it's a little bit of a turn,
so you just ignore the problem.
but, you should not ignore the problem.
If you do that, if the slope is a little steep, the turn will loosen the edge.
Tail will chatter.
You should never practice like that,
and if you feel like your rear leg are stretched out,
think that I'm not leading properly with my upper body.
Look at your upper pelvis
and think that I'm not doing the right thing.
When entering the turn, put the edge properly.
Especially when you weigh yourself properly on the tail, you're actively leading it.
And if you look at what I'm on,
you can see that I'm generally looking at the direction of progress.
But most beginners with those symptoms may have to lead at you more than you think.
But that doesn't mean lead too much.
Because if you try to lead a lot of gaze from the beginning,
The tail will slip again.
Because excessive upper body leading becomes a sliding turn,
It can have side effects that cause the tail to slip.
You put your weight on the tail,
you enter the turn,
and if you think the tail is made edge grip,
then you're going to lead the upper body.
So be active in your upper body reading to prevent your rear leg from stretching out.
Two problems of heel-turn that I just explained.
More than 90% of people who don't have heel-turn are due to two problems.
Turn this part around, look at it 10 times, look at it 100 times.
I hope you don't really go through this.
Thank you
Okay~ Then when should we finish practicing to give an angulation with down?
I think it would be nice if we could find a balance
where our hips could be as close to the slope
as possible to about 10 to 20 cm on the slope,
assuming that we don't hold our hands when we're doing the Angulation with down.
If you are practicing that much
This next step is up and down. In other words, enter the turn while with up,
when you get closer to the slope while practicing gradually down
I'm going to try it once in the next time until I practice my hands on my hands.
Then, practice hard
See you next time
Thank you